
export const QnA : {
    question: String,
    answer: String
}[] = [
    {
        question: "What services does Helping Hands India offer?",
        answer: "Helping Hands India provides reliable, professional household assistance, including housemaids, drivers, and housekeeping personnel, tailored to individual household needs."
    },
    {
        question: "How are the workers selected and vetted?",
        answer: "We follow a rigorous selection process, including background checks, reference verification, and skill assessments, to ensure trustworthy, skilled, and reliable personnel for your home."
    },
    {
        question: "Can I choose the helper based on specific requirements?",
        answer: "Yes, you can specify your preferences and needs, and we will match you with a suitable helper who meets your criteria."
    },
    {
        question: "Are the workers insured or covered for medical emergencies?",
        answer: "Yes, all our workers are provided with medical insurance and are covered under Provident Fund (PF) to ensure their well-being and peace of mind for our clients."
    },
    {
        question: "How does Helping Hands India ensure the safety and security of my home?",
        answer: "We take safety very seriously and conduct extensive background checks on each worker. Additionally, we provide training focused on privacy and respectful conduct within clients’ homes."
    },
    {
        question: "What if I am not satisfied with the service provided?",
        answer: "Customer satisfaction is our priority. If you’re not satisfied, please reach out to us, and we’ll work to resolve the issue or provide a replacement if needed."
    },
    {
        question: "How are service payments and contracts handled?",
        answer: "Payments can be made through secure channels on our website, and contracts can be arranged based on short-term or long-term requirements. Detailed options are available during the booking process."
    },
    {
        question: "What should I do if there’s an emergency or issue with my helper?",
        answer: "In case of any emergencies or issues, you can contact our 24/7 customer support team, who will assist and respond promptly to address the situation."
    },
    {
        question: "Can I cancel or reschedule a service?",
        answer: "Yes, you can cancel or reschedule services through our website or customer service. We recommend checking our cancellation and rescheduling policy for more details."
    },
    {
        question: "How does Helping Hands India handle worker replacement requests?",
        answer: "If you need a replacement due to a helper’s absence or other reasons, we will arrange an alternative at the earliest convenience. Just contact our customer support team for assistance."
    }
]
